SAHRUL RAMDAN

Subang, West Java, 41252

(M) +62 8139 4683 395 (E) sahrulramdan.75@gmail.com

(L) https://linkedin.com/in/sahrul-ramdan-2012

(W) https://itsahrul.id

Professional Summary -

A persistent person who loves to solve problems by crafting innovative digital products that can help people. Experienced in designing and developing an app in the early stage until finished. Problem-solver and love to think creatively.

Education

2019-2023

Universitas Subang – Subang (GPA: 3,72)

Bachelor of Computer Science: Information Technology

Experience

06/2023 - 09/2023 PDAM TKR Kab.Tangerang - Tangerang, Indonesia

Fullstack Developer – Part Time (ReactJS, MongoDB, NodeJS, ExpressJS)

- Developed an App that can automatically converting raw data into database using Sheet
- Developed a Learning Management System that has a feature for exam until reporting.

08/2023 - 08/2023 Gigih 3.0 Goto Impact Foundation - Remote

Fullstack Developer – Internship (ReactJS, MongoDB, NodeJS, ExpressJS)

 Make a replication for Tokopedia Play Clone (https://www.tokopedia.com/play/channels)

11/2022 - Current

PT Unmute Visual - Tangerang, Indonesia

Fullstack Developer – Full Time (ReactJS, MongoDB, NodeJS, ExpressJS)

- Make a beautiful website for advertisement using ReactJS and Framer Motion
- Make a company profile website using ReactJS, TailwindCSS, and Framer Motion
- Make an automation app for automatically collecting leads data from Facebook using ExpressJS and MongoDB
- Creating App for Business support in Fotolaku called "Fotolaku App Enterprise" using MERN Stack

08/2022 - 09/2022

Delipel Tastynas - Subang - West Java, Indonesia Fullstack Developer – Freelance (Laravel, MySQL)

- Make a gorgeous Store Profile Website using Laravel
- Maintenance server for Delipel Tastynas Website

Core Qualifications

Language: JavaScript, TypeScript, PHP, SQL

Library: React.js, Node.js

Framework: Next.js, ExpressJS, Laravel

Database: MongoDB, Postgresql, MySQL, SQLite

Styling: CSS, TailwindCSS, Chakra UI, Styled Components, Bootstrap

Tool: Git, Docker, Figma, Framer

Accomplishments

- 2nd Place Blog Design Competition awarded by STMIK Subang. Creating a stunning blog design that is created purely by HTML and CSS only.
- 4th Place National Web Design Competition awarded by Faculty of Electro Universitas Negeri Semarang. Live code for 2 days create a website that introduces the original Subang musical instrument by adding interactivity to playing the instrument.
- Best Participant of Frontend Developer Class in Week 3 held by Jabar Coding Camp
- Best Participant of Frontend Developer Class in Week 5 held by Jabar Coding Camp

Languages

Indonesia (First Language), Sundanese (Native), English (Excellent)